Welcome back.
歡迎回來。
In this section, we're going to complete
在本節中 ， 我們將完成
the content of our email and correct some problems that sneak in along the way.
電子郵件的內文和修正一些一直以來都被我們忽略的問題
While you were completing the challenges,
當你完成挑戰，
we added some new content.
我們增加了一些新的內容。
We've added a phone number, an unsubscribe link,
我們添加了一個電話號碼 ， 一個取消訂閱鏈接 ，
and some contact information.
以及一些聯絡資訊。
To do this, we created a new table with three rows,
要做到這一點，我們創造了一個有三行的表格，
with one cell each for each bit of content.
其中每個欄位有各自的內容。
In looking at the code that we wrote for the phone number,
來看看我們用來顯示電話號碼的程式碼，
we added this as plain text.
我們用純文字的格式來增加。
However, if we test it in Apple Mail,
但是，如果我們在Apple Mail中測試，
we're surprised to see that it's now a link.
我們很驚訝地看到會有一個連結。
What's happening here is Apple's preprocessor adds HTML to convert that text into a link.
是這樣的，Apple的預處理器加入HTML讓文字變成連結
Now we have a link in our email, but it
現在在電子郵件中有連結，但它
but it doesn't match our design.
但他並沒有和我們的設計相匹配。
We don't have access to the HTML that created the link,
我們沒有讀取創建連結的HTML，
but Apple Mail does support CSS in the style tag,
但Apple Mail支持在中的CSS，
so we can target all anchor tags and apply a color to them.
所以我們可以指定所有和應用顏色於程式中。
Now that we see this, we're thinking maybe
現在我們看到，我們可以想像也許...
it would be better if this text was white.
文字是白色的會更好一點。
We still don't have access to
我們還是沒有讀取
HTML that created this link, but we know where it's going to be,
創造了此連結的HTML，但我們知道他要放在哪
so to counter this behavior,
所以要對付這種行為 ，
we can wrap the phone number text in a span and then use that class
我們可以將電話號碼拉進，然後用其類別
to give that text a specific style.
設定特定樣式給內容。
Now we can see that our phone number
現在我們可以看到，我們的電話號碼
link has changed to white, while the unsubscribe link remained purple.
連結底線已更改為白色， 而取消訂閱連結依然是紫色。
This is exactly what we wanted.
這正是我們想要的。
Sometimes you want to set font size smaller than 14 pixels.
有時你想要設置字體大小比14px更小 。
Unfortunately, some clients won't allow this.
不幸的是， 某些客戶端將不會允許這樣 。
To show an example of this, we have set our font size to four pixels.
顯示了這樣一個例子，我們設置字體大小為4px
If we were to view this email in Gmail using Chrome,
如果我們要在Chrome中打開Gmail瀏覽，
we would see that it's rendering the text at four pixels.
我們會看到它在是以4px的樣子呈現。
However, if we look at it in Apple Mail,
但是 ， 如果我們在Apple Mail中讀取
we can see that it's not, and it's adjusted it to 14 pixels.
我們可以看到它並不是4px，他被調整為14px。
There are vendor-specific properties that exist to override these defaults.
有些內建屬性的存在直接的覆蓋這些預設值。
WebKit and Microsoft allow a text size adjustment to none,
不允許WebKit和微軟文字大小的調整 。
that would make it so our text will render at the specific pixel value that we set.
這將使我們的本文將會呈現為我們設定的樣子。
With this property in place, we can
更改了這樣的屬性後
we can see that Apple Mail will now render our footer text at four pixels.
我們可以看到Apple Mail將會顯示4px的文字大小在頁尾的部分
If we look at our email in Gmail using Chrome,
如果我們使用Chrome來開啟Gmail
we can see that there was no link added to the phone number,
我們可以看到，電話號碼是沒有加連結的
and our font sizes are the way that we want them.
而我們的字體大小是我們想要的樣子。
If we then look at it in Apple Mail,
如果我們再看看它在Apple Mail中的樣子，
we see that we do have our link, with our white color
我們可以看到，這是有連結且是白色的字，
and our smaller text size.
以及較小的字體。
Now it's your turn to tackle some edge cases in the challenges.
現在輪到你在挑戰中解決一些邊緣案件。
Take that, slide.
拿去....幻!燈!片!
Go to your home.
去...去...去...你家啦！
What is he talking about?
030 他是在講啥鬼...
Where —
哪裡 -。
In this section, we're going to — ooh.
在本節中 ， 我們將 .. 哦 。
Hey.
嘿 :目